(Claire:)Give me a call,
we'll get together.
(Raj:)Yeah, great.
See ya.
(Raj:)Yeah, bye.
(Howard:)What are you doing?
(Howard:)You have a girlfriend.
(Raj:)So?
So,
(Howard:)how do you think she'd feel
(Howard:)about you helping a beautiful
girl with her screenplay?
(Raj:)I wouldn't say
she's beautiful.
(Howard:)Really? You don't think
she's attractive?
(Raj:)I do. I just wouldn't
tell my girlfriend.
(Penny:)Constance, are you sure
I can't pour you some wine?
(Meemaw:)Oh, no wine for me.
(Meemaw:)Sheldon's bringing me
my whiskey.
(Sheldon:)Here you go, Meemaw.
I made it
(Sheldon:)just how you like...
(Sheldon:)a lot in a glass.
(Meemaw:)Thank you, Moon Pie.
Um, curious.
(Amy:)Why do you call Sheldon
“Moon Pie?”
'Cause he's so nummy-nummy.
BOTH:
She could just eat him up.
And I call her “Meemaw”"
(Sheldon:)because, well, just,
well, look at her.
(Meemaw:)It's interesting that
(Meemaw:)Leonard and Penny know
about his nickname
(Meemaw:)and you don't.